Guide to the Yale Medical Library Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Medical Library, records
1948-1987
RU 94
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
17.5
The records consist of annual reports, minutes, accreditation records, budgets, and correspondence, including files of Frederick G. Kilgour and Stanley D. Truelson as directors of the Yale Medical Library. A significant number of records relate to Kilgour's involvement with early library automation efforts. Other records pertain to Kilgour's published writings on library automation, the history of science and technology, and library administrative concerns.
Yale Medical Library
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-D (YRG 32-D), Records of Yale school and department libraries and collections.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of annual reports, minutes, accreditation records, budgets, and correspondence, including files of Frederick G. Kilgour and Stanley D. Truelson as directors of the Yale Medical Library. A significant number of records relate to Kilgour's involvement with early library automation efforts. Other records pertain to Kilgour's published writings on library automation, the history of science and technology, and library administrative concerns.
Academic libraries -- Departmental libraries; Libraries -- Automation; Medical libraries; Kilgour, Frederick G.; Truelson, Stanley D.; Yale Medical Library
- Outgoing correspondence, 1969-1976; Accession 1978-A-019
  - 1969 January (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1969 February (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1969 March (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1969 April (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1969 May (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1969 June (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1969 July (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1969 August (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1969 September (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1969 October (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1969 November (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1969 December (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1970 January (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1970 February (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1970 March (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1970 April (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1970 May (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1970 June (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1970 July (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 1970 August (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1970 September (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 1970 December (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 1971 January (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1971 February (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1971 March (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1971 April (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1971 May (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1971 June (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1971 July (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1971 August (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1971 September (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 1972 May (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 1972 June (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 1972 July (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 1972 August (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 1972 September (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 1972 October (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 1972 November (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 1972 December (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 1973 January (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 1973 February (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 1973 March (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 1973 April (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 1973 May (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 1973 June-July (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 1973 August (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - 1973 September (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - 1973 October (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 1973 November (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - 1973 December (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - 1974 January (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1974 February (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1974 March (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1974 April (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1974 May (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1974 June (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1974 July (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1974 August (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 1974 September (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1974 October (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1974 November (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1974 December (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 1975 January (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 1975 February (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 1975 March (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 1975 April (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 1975 May (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - 1975 June (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 1975 July (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 1975 August (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 1975 September (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 1975 October (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - 1975 November (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 1975 December (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - 1976 March (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - 1976 April (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - 1976 May (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 1976 June (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 1976 July (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 1976 August (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - 1976 September (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Records, 1948-1987; Accession 1990-A-067
  - Accreditation, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annual reports
    - 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Annual statistics: Yates, Johnnie, 1980-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Associates annual meetings
    - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1974-1976 (special) (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Audit, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Audit, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Budgets
    - 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 1966-1979 travel (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Campbell Collection, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Catalog, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Cataloging
    - 1964-1974 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Maintenance, 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Subject cataloging in depth, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Coffin, Charles A., Fund, 1948-1979 (Box 1, Folder 33 - 35)
    - Collection Review Project: Responses, Lee Ash, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Committee, Library
    - 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - 1980 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Consulting, 1966-1975 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Departmental Libraries, 1966-1975 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Foreign dissertations, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Fry Collection grant, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Gifts proposed, 1966-1973 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - New England Regional Medical Library Service (NERMLS): Document delivery, 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Periodicals
    - Cancellations and possible withdrawals, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Responses and withdrawal list, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Pledges, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Psychology cancellations, responses, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 55 - 56)
    - Staff manual, 1966-1975 (Box 2, Folder 57 - 59)
    - Streeter Collection, 1958-1974 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - User Guide
    - The Nursing Literature, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Other local libraries, 1970-1972, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Records, circa 1954-1967; Accession 19ND-A-142
  - MAD - programming, Circa 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - IBM 1401, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Computer - CHY programs, distribution of, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Kungliga Biblioteket (Lars Tynell), 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - St. Louis University library, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The University of Arizona, School of Medicine, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - University of California at Santa Cruz, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - University of Kentucky, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - University of Rochester, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - University of Saskatchewan Regina campus, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Washington University, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Yale University: Economic Growth Library, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence and printed materials (parts 1 - 14), 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 13-26)
  - Computer, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - CHY, medical bibliographic informational retrieval system, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Curran, Ann T, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Esterquest, Ralph, 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Fleming, Thomas P., 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - King, Robert Norman, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence and printed materials (parts I - 4), 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 33-36)
  - Kilgour, library of congress, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Kilgour, correspondence, 1957-1964 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Library resources, annual reports, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - CLR, recent developments, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, D., 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Divett, Robert, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - History of Science department, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, E., 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Encyclopedia (McGraw - Hill, Daniel Lapedes), 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Grants and contracts, general, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Meeting proposal - NSF, April 1967 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Office of Education, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Grants, general, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Contract, computer analysis of biomedical book and journal use, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Project report #2, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Grants, Columbia - Harvard, Yale project, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Columbia, Harvard, Yale Grant, correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Grant request (parts I through 3), 1962 (Box 2, Folder 14-16)
  - Association of research library, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - ADI, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Advisory board of library clearing house, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Bill 1960 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Bill 1961 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Bill 1962 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bill 1963 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bill 1964 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Bill 1965 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Medical Library Assistance Act of, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - American Libraries Association (parts 1 and 2), 1958-1966 (Box 2, Folder 28-29)
  - ALA relations committee (parts I and II), 1959-1961 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Washington newsletter, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - ALA recruiting, 1959-1962 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - ASA subcomm./machine-Input records Z39, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Old business, from Z39.2, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Argonne National laboratories, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondences, B-C (parts I and II), 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 8-9)
  - Committee on central statistical services, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Manual of tumor nomenclature and coding, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - COLA, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - IV CHY computer, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - CY consultant, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Computers (parts I through III), 1965 (Box 3, Folder 15-17)
  - Publicity - project, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Computer #2, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Computer #1 (parts I and II), 1962 (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
  - Computer, 120 character print chain, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Computer compatibility committee, NLM and CHY, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 870 document writer, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Registered IBM confidential, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Mitre 1962 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Cataloging worksheet, Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Computer programming, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Bulletin program, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - CHY-1, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - CHY-1, examples of short title t-addr. problem, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - CHY, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - CHY-2, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 4K-2T sort, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Punch program, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Illustrations, captions, and sources, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Introduction, 1954-1957 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Picture captions (parts I and II), 1954-1957 (Box 4, Folder 9-10)
  - Industry, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Steam vessels and locomotives, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Iron and Steel, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Transportation (parts I through III), 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 14-16)
  - Electrical Engineering (parts 1 through 4), Undated (Box 4, Folder 17-20)
  - Sanitary and Hydraulic Engineering XIII, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Construction XIV, Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Reflections XV, Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Gold Schmidt cataloges 126, 125, 123, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Rare books and early Mss., catalogue 166, Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Medicine and surgery, pharmacology, astronomy, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Engineering in History, book, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Excerpta Medica foundation, 1956-1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Engineering in History, contents, preface, chapter 1, pp. 1-9, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Engineering in History, chapter 2, Urban Society, pp. 10-40, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Engineering in History, chapter 3, Greek Engineering, pp. 41-64, Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Engineering in History, chapter 4, Imperial Civilization (Rome), pp. 65-107, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Engineering in History, chapter 5, Power Revolution, pp. 108-138, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Engineering in History, chapter 6, Foundations for Industry, pp. 139-182, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Engineering in History, chapter 7, Industrial Revolution, pp. 183-224, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Engineering in History, chapter 9, Locomotives and Steamships, pp. 278-331, Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Engineering in History, chapter 8, Industrial Transportation, pp.225-277, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Engineering in History, chapter 10, Iron and Steel, pp.332-370, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Engineering in History, chapter 11, Electricity, pp.371-430, Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Engineering in History, chapter 12, Modern Transportation, pp. 431-493, Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Engineering in History, chapter 13, Hydraulic and Sanitary Engineering, pp. 494-537, Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Engineering in History, chapter 14, Modern Construction, pp. 538-572, Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Reflections, chapter 15, Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Drafts, chapter 3, Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Drafts, chapter 1 and 2, Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Engineering in History 4 (new), Imperial Civilization (Rome), Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Drafts, chapter 5, Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Drafts, chapter 6, Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Drafts, chapter 7, Undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Illustrations for Engineering in History (parts 1 through 4), Undated (Box 5, Folder 23-26)
  - Kilgoun papers, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Index of printers and publishers (parts 1 through 3), Undated (Box 5, Folder 28-30)
  - Publications, 1961-1966 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Requests, 1960-1966 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Machine aided technical processing system and interim report, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Basic systems assumptions, Columbia, Harvard, Yale, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Catalogue subject searches in the Yale Medical Library, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Comparison between subject headings, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Computer applications in Biomedical libraries, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Comuterization of book catalogues, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Computers for the Humanities, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Density of library book use, 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Clinic on library applications of data processing, University of Illinois, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Disappearance of unbound journals, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - History of Engineering documents, 1954-1965 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Handbook of medical library practice, 1957-1965 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - W. Harvey and his contributions, 1961-1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Library catalogue production on small computers (parts 1 and 2), 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
  - Library of the Medical Institute of Yale College (parts 1 and 2), 1960-1965 (Box 6, Folder 11-12)
  - Margwal punch card form, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Machines and Processes article, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Mental illness, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Mechanization of cataloguing procedures (parts 1 and 2), 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
  - California, research evaluation, group 29-30; Pasadena, California, November 1965 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Work session: A proposed format for a standard catalogue record, November 22, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Institute on I.R. in biomedical sciences, University of Minnesota, November 10-13, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Health sciences information center, University of Michigan, November 1965 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Trips, Potomac Valley; Washington, D.C., October 30, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - FID congress, Washington D.C., October 10-15, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Burlington, Vermont, October 21, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Dillon group, Detroit, July 2-5, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - MLA convention, Philadelphia, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Countway library dedication, May 26-27, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - IBM symposium; Yorktown Heights, N.Y., May 2-4, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Second annual national colloquium of information retrieval, April 23-24, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - MLA on NLM committee; Bethesda, MD, January 28, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - AAAS and society for History of Technology, December 27-28, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Harvard library club, December 3, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - ADI Philadelphia, October 5-8, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Public and library mechanization, May 25-27, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Clinic on library applications of data processing, April 26-29, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Yale medical alumni in New England, October 16, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - IBM library executive seminar, October 3, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - ADI meeting; Chicago (parts 1 and 2), October 1963 (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
  - Second international congress, med. library, June 1963 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Visitors, II international congress, June 1963 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - The automation of library systems, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - University of Illinois, clinic on library applications, April 28-May 1, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - IBM data processing and information retrieval (parts 1 and 2), 1963 (Box 7, Folder 10-11)
  - Bethesda, Medlars, Washington, April 3-5, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Hollywood by the sea, December 12-14, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Boston, New England conference on community health records management, November 15-17, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Minneapolis, November 7-8, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Rochester, October 11-13, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Minnesota, information retrieval, September 18, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Tenth international congress of the History of Science, August 26-September 2, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Chicago, June 5-9, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Documentation, November 6-8, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Site visits, general (individual site visit trips follow), April 2, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Site visit, excerpta medica foundation, April 25, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Site visit, University of Pennsylvania, October 10, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Scientific information committee meeting; Sheraton motor Inn; Baltimore, MD, December 15-17, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Site visit, Columbia, February 26-27, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Lehigh University site visit; Bethlehem, Pennsylvania, February 1, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Documentation, February 1965 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Site visit, St. Louis, April 1, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Site visit, advisory council, April 1965 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Pittsburgh, site visit (parts 1 and 2), 1965 (Box 8, Folder 2-3)
  - Site visit, Chicago, September 19-20, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Site visit, Minneapolis, Minnesota (A. Lazerow), October 8-9, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Cleveland, Goldwyn, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - John's Hopkins, site visit; Baltimore, MD, December 15-17, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Rutgers, The State University, 1966-167 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - University of Massachussetts, Mr. Frederick Kilgour, April 13, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Roger Williams General Hospital, Mr. Frederick Kilgour, April 4, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Site visit, John's Hopkins, information center, hearing, speech, etc..., 1967 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - George Washington University, Mr. Frederick G. Kilgour, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - UCSF, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Kilgour; Methesda, MD, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Grants, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - IFI, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Advisory committee of scientific publications, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Advisory committee second meeting, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Gerontology, Kilgour, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Advisory committee on scientific publications, general 1, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Advisory committee on scientific publications, general 2 (parts 1 through 3), 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 21-23)
  - ACSP subcommittee, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - ACSP, Bethesda, April 28, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Site visit, Bethesda, MD; Mr. Kilgour, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Site visit, Detroit; Mr. Kilgour, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Advisory committee on scientific publications meeting (part 1 of 2), May 16, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Advisory committee on scientific publications meeting (part 2 of 2), May 16, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - PHS advisory committee on scientific publications (parts 1 and 2), April 28, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 2-3)
  - Review of contracts, October 5, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - PHS advisory committee on scientific publications (parts 1 and 2), January 27, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
  - PHS advisory committee on scientific publications (parts 1 and 2), 1964 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - Washington, D.C., September 29-30, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Aqvaic biology serials, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Research and grants, 1961-1964 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - ACSP, May 21-22, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Advisory committee on scientific publications meeting, general, October 11, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Seven proposals (parts 1 through 3), 1963 (Box 9, Folder 14-16)
  - Associated Universities, Inc... (T. Reith Glennan), 1966 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - American Library Association, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Association of College and Research Libraries, 1954-1967 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Committee on library automation, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Newsletters on library automation (parts 1 through 4), 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 21-24)
  - Computer center, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Computer center advisory committee (parts 1 and 2), 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 26-27)
  - Computerization of acquisitions procedures, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - EDUCOM, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Conn. research proposal, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - GRANT, design of techniques for investigating use of bio-medical books and journals, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - NIH, hierarchic interlock of MeSH and LC subject headings, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - GRANT, programming computerized catalogues of C-H-Y Med. Libs. NSF, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Kilgour, Frederick G.; correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - GRANT, programming computerized medical library catalogues - NIH, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - NSF, research study, recorded use of volumes in a University library, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Off. Education, user requirement study, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Ted Hines, Filing, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Herner report, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 11)